Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings, 545120
  - Video 050: CCTV Apr 24, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1680; 546030 (Box 80)
  - Video 051: CCTV Apr 24, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: Kung Fu Match II, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1681; 546029 (Box 80)
  - Video 052: CCTV May 1, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1682; 546028 (Box 80)
  - Video 053: CCTV May 1, 1977 Broadcast tape Profile: Hsia Yang, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1683; 546027 (Box 81)
  - Video 054: CCTV May 8, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1684; 546026 (Box 81)
  - Video 055: CCTV May 8, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: A Talk with Two Mothers, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1685; 546025 (Box 81)
  - Video 056: CCTV May 15, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1686; 546024 (Box 81)
  - Video 057: CCTV May 15, 1977 Broadcast tape Drama "The World of Ah Sing", May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1687; 546023 (Box 81)
  - Video 058: CCTV May 22, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1688; 546022 (Box 81)
  - Video 059: CCTV May 29, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1689; 546021 (Box 81)
  - Video 060: CCTV Jun 5, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1690; 546020 (Box 81)
  - Video 061: CCTV Jun 12, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1691; 546019 (Box 81)
  - Video 062: CCTV Jun 12, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1692; 546018 (Box 81)
  - Video 063: CCTV Jun 19, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1693; 546017 (Box 81)
  - Video 064: CCTV Jun 26, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1694; 546016 (Box 81)
  - Video 065: CCTV Jul 3, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1695; 546015 (Box 81)
  - Video 066: CCTV Jul 3, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1696; 546014 (Box 81)
  - Video 067: CCTV Jul 10, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1697; 546013 (Box 81)
  - Video 068: CCTV Jul 10, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1698; 546012 (Box 81)
  - Video 069: CCTV Jul 17, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1699; 546011 (Box 81)
  - Video 070: CCTV Jul 17, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1700; 546010 (Box 81)
  - Video 071: CCTV Jul 24, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1701; 546009 (Box 81)
  - Video 072: CCTV Jul 31, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1702; 546008 (Box 81)
  - Video 073: CCTV Aug 7, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Village Voice in Chinatown, Teng and Wah and China, Construction site demonstration, CIA on mind control, New York black out, Bombing, Occupations, Nixon's interview, San Francisco hotel strike, cultural, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1703; 546007 (Box 81)
  - Video 074: CCTV Aug 14, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1704; 546006 (Box 81)
  - Video 075: CCTV Aug 21, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1705; 546005 (Box 81)
  - Video 076: CCTV Aug 21, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: CCTV Production and Performance, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1706; 546004 (Box 81)
  - Video 077: CCTV Aug 28, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1707; 546003 (Box 81)
  - Video 078: CCTV Aug 28, 1977 Broadcast tape Drama "War and Peace", May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1708; 546002 (Box 81)
  - Video 079: Sep 4, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1709; 546001 (Box 82)
  - Video 080: Sep 4, 1977 Broadcast tape, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1710; 546000 (Box 82)
  - Video 081: Sep 9, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Mayoral candidate campaign at Silver Palace, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1711; 545999 (Box 82)
  - Video 082: Sep 11, 1977 Broadcast tape Year End Special, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1712; 545998 (Box 82)
  - Video 083: Sep 11, 1977 Broadcast tape First Anniversary, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1713; 545997 (Box 82)
  - Video 084: Oct 2, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Discussion: Mayoral candidate in Chinatown, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1714; 545996 (Box 82)
  - Video 085: Oct 9, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1715; 545995 (Box 82)
  - Video 086: Oct 9, 1977 Broadcast tape Cultural Festival (CPC Festival II) (Repeat), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1716; 545994 (Box 82)
  - Video 087: Nov 1977 Broadcast tape, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1717; 545993 (Box 82)
  - Video 088: Nov 6, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Mayoral candidate campaign, Carter's increase of minimum wage, Health Clinic's fund raising dinner, Mobilization for Youth demonstrations against Union, Hong Kong police complaints against corruption, New York, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1718; 545992 (Box 82)
  - Video 089: Nov 13, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Ed Koch elected as mayor of New York City, Hong Kong police demonstration against corruption problems, photo exhibit at Center Street, Social Services focus on mental health, Taiwan donated a painting to St., Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1719; 545991 (Box 82)
  - Video 090: Nov 20, 1977 Broadcast tape News (, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1720; 545990 (Box 82)
  - Video 091: Nov 27, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Koch and campaign staff appointment, Asian American women conference, Middle East, Lisa Chow, Social Services interview with Mrs. Fong Min, Manpower training program), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1721; 545989 (Box 82)
  - Video 092: Dec 4, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Lincoln's Savings Bank Grand Opening, Bakke Case), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1722; 545988 (Box 82)
  - Video 093: Dec 11, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Sadat and Begin peace talks, Social Services with Dr. Yang Lung San on physical health, Liz Young and Ken Chin demonstration, Peking Opera at Merrill Bertrum), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1723; 545987 (Box 82)
  - Video 094: Dec 25, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Garment Workers Union 5 Chinese Board of Directors elected, CPC Adult Education Center graduation ceremony, Social Services interview with Mrs. Chan Duk Wah from the National Bank of North America), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1724; 545986 (Box 82)
  - Video 095: Jan 8, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Carter's trip to Iran, Poland, India, etc., return of the Crown to Hungry by the U.S., Carey's proposal for income tax reduction, Edward Koch's executive order for equal employment for gay/lesbians, Chinatown, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1725; 545985 (Box 82)
  - Video 096: Jan 15, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Edward Koch agrees to wage increase for city workers, Vietnam and Cambodia, Liz Young and Ken Chin Press Conference, Pang Jik Kun postponement of hearings, California proposes banning of smoking, Social Servi, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1726; 545984 (Box 82)
  - Video 097: Jan 22, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Carter's State of the Union address, debating the Middle East question, Pang case press conference with Morgenthau and interview with MB Lee, conflict between Vietnam and Cambodia, death of Herbert H. Humprhy, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1727; 545983 (Box 82)
  - Video 098: Jan 29, 2978 Broadcast tape News (Interview with Goji at the Democratic National Committee in Washington, DC, Ten Sau Pin visits Burma and Nepal, United Democratic Party Breakfast and interview with Carol Bellamy and Virginia Kee, Bella Abzug, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1728; 545982 (Box 82)
  - Video 099: Feb 5, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Ed Koch goes to Washington, Pan Am has low fare to the Orient and around the World trip, Old Age Center year-end dinner, Jimmy Carter on the Middle East, Asian American Film Festival interview with Tom Tam, In, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1729; 545981 (Box 82)
  - Video 100: Feb 5, 1978 Broadcast tape News (New Year Celebration by the Chinese students at Pace college including singing and karate by William Louie and dancing by the New York Chinese Dance Company, CPB meeting at the Summit Hotel with speakers Mrs., Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1730; 545980 (Box 82)
  - Video 101: Feb 12, 1978 Broadcast tape New Year welcome, CPC New Year dinner at Silver Palace with interviews with CPC's Charles Wang, Alan Cohen by Corky Lee, An introduction of the Cultural Festival program, Panama Canal Issue, Pace Hispanic Ballet by, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1731; 545979 (Box 82)
  - Video 102: Feb 19, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Nixon's Board, Jimmy carter decides to sell Arab the latest weapon, Ali lost the fight, Four Seas Players, Asian American Dance Company), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1732; 545978 (Box 82)
  - Video 103: Feb 19, 1978 Broadcast tape Play, cuid1733; 545977 (Box 82)
  - Video 104: Feb 26, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1734; 545976 (Box 82)
  - Video 105: March 5, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1735; 545975 (Box 83)
  - Video 106: March 5, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1736; 545974 (Box 83)
  - Video 107: March 12, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Women's Day), cuid1737; 545973 (Box 83)
  - Video 108: March 12, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1738; 545972 (Box 83)
  - Video 109: March 19, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1739; 545971 (Box 83)
  - Video 110: March 19, 1978 Broadcast tape Philippine Immigrants by Leonardo Ignacio, cuid1740; 545970 (Box 83)
  - Video 111: March 26, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1741; 545969 (Box 83)
  - Video 112: March 26, 1978 Broadcast tape Asian American Film Festival: The Journey (cartoon), Take Me, cuid1742; 545968 (Box 83)
  - Video 113: April 2, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1743; 545967 (Box 83)
  - Video 114: April 2, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1744; 545966 (Box 83)
  - Video 115: April 9, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1745; 545965 (Box 83)
  - Video 116: April 9, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1746; 545964 (Box 83)
  - Video 117: April 16, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1747; 545963 (Box 83)
  - Video 118: April 16, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1748; 545962 (Box 83)
  - Video 119: April 23, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1749; 545961 (Box 83)
  - Video 120: April 23, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1750; 545960 (Box 83)
  - Video 121: April 30, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1751; 545959 (Box 83)
  - Video 122: April 30, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1752; 545958 (Box 83)
  - Video 123: May 7, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1753; 545957 (Box 83)
  - Video 124: May 7, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1754; 545956 (Box 83)
  - Video 125: May 14, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1755; 545955 (Box 83)
  - Video 126: May 21, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1756; 545954 (Box 83)
  - Video 127: May 28, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1757; 545953 (Box 83)
  - Video 128: May 28, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1758; 545952 (Box 83)
  - Video 129: June 4, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1759; 545951 (Box 83)
  - Video 130: June 4, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1760; 545950 (Box 83)
  - Video 131: June 11, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1761; 545949 (Box 83)
  - Video 132: June 11, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1762; 545948 (Box 83)
  - Videos 133-145 (Portapacks), Jun 18-Sep 3, 1978; cuid1763; 545947 (Box 84)
  - Videos 146-158 (Portapacks), Sep 17-Dec 24, 1978; cuid1764; 545946 (Box 85)
  - Videos 159-171 (Portapacks), Jan 7-Mar 18, 1979; cuid1765; 545945 (Box 86)
  - Videos 172-183 (Portapacks), Mar 18-May 27, 1979; cuid1766; 545944 (Box 87)
  - Videos 184-195 (Portapacks), Jun 3-Jul 22, 1979; cuid1767; 545943 (Box 88)
  - Videos 196-207 (Portapacks), Jul 29-Sep 25, 1979; cuid1768; 545942 (Box 89)
  - Videos 208-221 (Portapacks), Sep 30-Dec 23, 1979; cuid1769; 545941 (Box 90)
  - Video 222: CCTV, January 6, 1980; Cuid9268 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9268)
    Scope and Contents
    This episode includes three parts: street interviews, a 35-minute film, and an announcement section. In the street interviews, two hosts interview people about the newspapers they read, their views on international and domestic news, their impressions of last year, and their hopes for the coming year. The second part of the episode is a Curtis Choy film Dupont Guy: The Schiz of Grant Avenue (1976). The film narrates the struggles and experiences of being Chinese American.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 52 minutes
  - Video 223: CCTV, January 13, 1980; Cuid9269 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9269)
    This episode includes several parts: street interviews, coverage of a photo exhibition and a variety show, a 9-minute documentary, and an announcement section. In the street interviews, two hosts interview people about their views on subways in the city. The photo exhibition shows two Chinese photographers' works that depict life in Chinatown, including sweatshop laborers and street demonstrations for employment equality. The variety show is called China Nite and is organized by a local middle school. The documentary film contains intertitles that read Brute Force Cybernetics presents Second Campaign and Berkeley May 1969.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 53 minutes
  - Video 224: CCTV, January 20, 1980; Cuid9270 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9270)
    This episode includes three parts: a news report on a local demonstration, a 19-minute documentary, and an announcement section. The first part covers housing issues faced by a group of Chinatown residents, who organized demonstrations against the landlord Thomas Sung. Interviews with the disaffected tenants and Thomas Sung () are included. The second part shows a documentary film Jenny (1977), which is produced by Japanese American Ginny Hashii. The documentary narrates the experiences of being Japanese American in the United States.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration 55 minutes.
  - Video 225: CCTV, January 27, 1980; Cuid9271 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9271)
    This episode includes three parts: street interviews, a Hong Kong film, and an announcement section. In the street interviews, two hosts interview people about heat provision in their apartments. Interviewees complain about having difficulties getting heat in the winter, and they suggest it is landlords' responsibility to take care of this matter. The second part of the episode is an Allen Fong () film The Wild Child () (1977). The film depicts the ups and downs of a young boy's life who lives with his grandmother in a rural village.
    Format: Umatic, Duration: 57 minutes
  - Video 226: CCTV, February 3, 1980; Cuid9272 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9272)
    This episode includes several parts: news reports on Chinese athletes visiting the United States and Chinese students having dinner gathering, a 26-minute Hong Kong film, coverage of a labor demonstration, and an announcement section. The first part reports the US-China Peoples Friendship Association receiving People's Republic of China athletes who for the first time attend the Winter Olympics. Interviews with athletes and officials from China are included. The second part covers a dinner gathering organized by the National Association of Chinese-Americans. The third part is an Allen Fong () film Song of Yuen Chau Chai () (1977), which depicts the lives of fishermen in Hong Kong. The fourth section covers a labor demonstration against a Chinese restaurant called House of Chan. Laborers demand recognition of their union by the employer.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 55 minutes
  - Video 227: CCTV, February 10, 1980; Cuid9273 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9273)
    This episode includes two parts: a travel program and coverage of a ceremony in New York City. The first part is a program called Travelogue (), the host introduces a skate rink in Coney Island in New York City, presumably the Abe Stark. Interviews with some skaters are included. The second part covers a ceremony in which President of the City Council Carol Bellamy presents awards to community art groups, including CCTV. The ceremony is held at the Marble Collegiate Church, 1 West 29th Street.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 61 minutes
  - Video 228: CCTV, February 17, 1980; Cuid9274 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9274)
    This episode features activities of Chinese people in New York City celebrating the lunar new year. Activities shown in the episode include singing and dancing shows, martial arts (Kung Fu), and a lion dance performance. The episode also includes interviews with the performers. In the last part, the host of the episode tells traditional stories relevant to the Chinese lunar new year (Year of the Monkey).
  - Video 229: CCTV, February 24, 1980; Cuid9275 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9275)
    This episode includes three parts: a segment on First Lady Rosalynn Carter's visit to Chinatown, another on a Yale University professor visiting Chinatown with students, and a feature on a Chinese culinary school. In the first part, a banquet is held in a Chinese restaurant to receive Mrs. Carter's visit; Mrs. Carter and others give speeches. The second part includes interviews with the Yale professor - who is Chinese - and the students. The third part features a special program called At Your Service (), which introduces culinary and English lessons offered by the China Institute. Interviews with the institute organizer and culinary lesson participants are included.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 58 minutes
  - Video 230: CCTV, March 2, 1980; Cuid9276 (Box 91, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9276)
    This episode includes four parts: street interviews, a lunar new year festival show, a banquet dinner, and an interview with a lawyer. In the first part, the hosts ask people what their views are on the robbery of Chinatown Lincoln Savings Bank. The second part presents a lunar new year performance show organized by the Better Chinatown Project (). The third part features a banquet organized by the Chinese American Chamber of Commerce to welcome Winter Olympic athletes from the People's Republic of China. Interviews with athletes are included. The last part is an interview with Benjamin Gim, a representative of the Chinese Lawyers Association.
  - Video 231: CCTV, March 9, 1980; Cuid9277 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9277)
    This episode includes three parts: a segment on First Lady Rosalynn Carter's visit to Chinatown, street interviews, and a 29-minute documentary. In the first part, a banquet is held at the Silver Palace restaurant to receive Mrs. Carter's visit. Mrs. Carter and other Chinese representatives give speeches. This is the first time the First Lady of the United States visits Chinatown for presidential election fundraising. In the second part, two hosts comment on the disadvantages of smoking and interview people about their views on smoking. The third part is a PBS documentary Emi (1979). The other name of the documentary is Pearls. It is directed by Michael Uno and Frank Nesbitt, about Japanese-American Emiko Tonooka's experience in a California internment camp during World War Two.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 59 minutes
  - Video 232: CCTV, March 16, 1980; Cuid9278 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9278)
    This episode includes three parts: interviews with children, a segment on a fundraising banquet, and a 35-minute film. In the first part, two hosts interview children and teenagers about their views on watching television. The second part is about a banquet held in Chinatown to support Ted Kennedy running for the presidential election. Present at the banquet include congressman John Murphy, and New York state Kennedy for president campaign manager Richard Donahue. The third part is a Curtis Choy film Dupont Guy: The Schiz of Grant Avenue (1976). The film narrates the struggles and experiences of being Chinese American.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 62 minutes
  - Video 233: CCTV, March 23, 1980; Cuid9279 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9279)
    This episode includes five parts: a segment on the visit of a Shanghai acrobatic theater, an interview with Chinese playwright Cao Yu (), coverage of an academic conference, and a special program on the 1980 census. The first part is about the Shanghai acrobatic troupe's US-tour show. The second part covers Chinese playwright Cao Yu's visit to Columbia University. An interview with Cao Yu is also included. The third part is about a conference organized by Asian Women United, a New York-based women's organization. The fourth part is a performance by Chinese singer Zi Wei (), who is also interviewed. Lastly, the episode includes advertisements to promote the 1980 census, with a special program on the history and operation of census (including interviews with census workers).
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 49 minutes
  - Video 234: CCTV, March 30, 1980; Cuid9280 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9280)
    This episode includes three parts: a special program about the 1980 census, a performance, and street interviews. In the first part, the host interviews three census program staff members. They introduce the mission, data collection process, and privacy protection measures of the 1980 census. The second part features a performance by singer Zi Wei (). The third part includes street interviews with Chinatown residents about their views on the 1980 census.
  - Video 235: CCTV, April 3, 1980; Cuid9281 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9281)
    This episode is a special program on an acrobatic troupe from Shanghai and their visit to the United States. Included in this episode are stage performances, a reception organized by Chinatown residents to welcome the members, and advertisements of a number of Chinatown stores sponsoring the program.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 54 minutes
  - Video 236: CCTV, April 6, 1980; Cuid9282 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9282)
    This episode has four parts: a report on an award presentation banquet in Chinatown, an interview with a Chinese playwright, street interviews, and a special program. In the first part, a banquet is held at the Silver Palace restaurant where the Council of Asian-American Women presents an award to Congresswoman Elizabeth Holtzman. Holtzman is interviewed about her views on immigration and refugee issues. The second part is an interview with Chinese playwright Cao Yu (). There are scenes from stage performances of Cao Yu's works - the English version of Sunrise () and Peking Man (). In the third part, a host interviews Chinatown residents about their views on the 1980 New York City transit strike. The last section is a special program about the 1980 census. The host interviews three census program staff members, asking them to provide details on the purpose and operation of the census.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 57 minutes
  - Video 237: CCTV, April 20, 1980; Cuid9283 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9283)
    This episode has four parts: a coverage of an award presentation banquet in Chinatown, excerpts of a cultural festival, a feature report about a vocational training school, and interviews with teenagers. In the first part, a banquet is held at the Silver Palace restaurant where the Council of Asian-American Women presents an award to Congresswoman Elizabeth Holtzman. Holtzman is interviewed about her views on immigration and refugee issues. The second part shows excerpts of a music cultural festival held at Shuang Wen School located in Manhattan's Chinatown. The third part is a feature program called At Your Service (), which covers a hotel management vocational training school. The school is operated by Jack Han. In the last part of this episode, two hosts interview children and teenagers about their views on watching television.
  - Video 238: CCTV, April 27, 1980; Cuid9284 (Box 92, Videocassettes (u-matic) Cuid9284)